게임을 사서 토르티지 섬을 돌아다녔는데
I bought the game, and I've been exploring the island of Tortage,
경비 대장을 어떻게 넘겨야 할지 모르겠어요
but I don't know how to get past the Guard Captain.
마법검은 가지고 있어요? - 아뇨, 지금 청동 단검인데요
Do you have the Enchanted Sword? - No, I have a bronze dagger.
청동 단검으로는 경비 대장 못 깨요
You can't slay the Guard with a bronze dagger.
지금 이건 대문에 열쇠 넣는 거랑 다를 게 없잖아요
My Lord, it's like the car key in your apartment door all over again.
알겠어요, 그 칼은 어떻게 구해요? - 미트라 사원에는 갔어요?
All right, how do I get the sword? - Have you been to the Temple of Mitra?
언덕 위에 이상한 사제들이 있던 곳이요?
Is that the place on the hill with the weird priest in front of it?
아뇨, 어디냐면.. 줘봐요 - 정말 고마워요
It's... Oh, for God's sakes, gimme. - Thank you-- I really appreciate.
이런 건 혼자서도 할 줄 알아야 해요
You're gonna have to learn to do these things for yourself.
잘난 척하지 말고 칼이나 찾아봐요
Don't patronize me-- just get the sword!
도대체 뭔 일이래?
What the frack?